I can't believe Ray is
the Iceblade Sorcerer...
one of the Seven Grands,
the best of the best.
He's not like me.
He's overcome a cruel past.
Just what I'd expect from you, Amelia!
The eldest daughter of the House Rose,
the leader of the three greatest families.
Not just a noble bloodline,
but also the promise of a bright future!
So wonderful!
They can expect all they want,
but I'll never amount to anything.
In reality, I'm completely empty inside.
Just like a...
...a bird in a cage.
Ow, my eyes!
My eyes!
Anyway, that Ray...
Isn't he supposed to be more flustered?
Or does this mean I'm not attractive enough?
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
Episode 6
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Dons a Mask
And how are you all doing today?
It's me, Carocaro!
Let's go over the topic of
the Magic Chevalier again!
The Magic Chevalier is a magic
sword-fighting tournament
held between three sorcery academies.
First-year students will compete
in the rookie bracket.
Second-year students and higher will
participate in the main tournament.
Usually, 16 contestants are selected
from each of the three academies.
But since last year's winner
was our own Rebecca Bradley,
our academy gets to pick not just five,
but six contestants!
That's so lucky!
They say overall, we're the strongest,
but Diom is an academy that
specializes in actual battle,
while Mercross specializes
in sorcery research.
Many students there go on to become researchers.
Well, anyway, we've all got our
own particular strengths,
so it should be a good competition.
The organizational staff might be doing the
non-glamorous job of supporting the faculty,
but they are the unsung heroes.
So, we're counting on you!
Now, let's get right to the qualifiers.
Ray, we've got to do our best!
Let's assign you all your tasks!
Yay! Fun fun!
Huh?
Miss Abbie!
What is it, Ray?
You know exactly what it is!
Why is... why is that woman... here?!
Oh, you mean Carol.
She happened to be free,
so I called her here.
It's also my responsibility to select
staff that will keep this academy safe.
Then, I will assist you!
But please, anyone but that woman!
I understand how you feel, but...
Miss Abbie, I'm sure you're also aware of this.
She's the only person I can't handle.
It's always been that way.
And on top of it all,
she has to be my homeroom teacher?
Relax.
Carol's brand of sorcery is
very convenient to have.
Plus, the students seem to like her, too.
Th-That's...
That's because they don't
know her true nature!
Anyway, please just fire her,
the sooner the better!
Did you really just say that, Ray?
That makes me so sad.
Miss Abbie!
Wait!
Sorry, but you'll have to give it up.
Let me pet you like I used to!
Despite being this way,
she's actually quite a talented sorcerer.
Who do you think is going to win this match?
I don't know her name, but I think
it will be the female student.
Her code assembly rate and
accuracy are on another level.
The guy keeps trying to attack her with
his sword, but he's still very clumsy.
Based on her overall power,
she's got the better chance here.
Oh.
Looks like they're done.
That's a bit creepy.
What is?
Don't "what is" me!
It's weird to know who will win a
fight mere seconds after it started.
Is it?
The difference in their
abilities was clear as day.
At this level, three seconds is usually
enough to determine how it will end.
Creepy...
Oh, this is the big one!
Miss Amelia!
Oh, it's over.
Even I can tell!
The winner is Amelia Rose.
Six seconds!
I know it's just an early round,
but Amelia is truly amazing.
Yes, however...
Victory is obvious.
But it doesn't look like that's
what she's thinking about...
She has the expression of someone
handling a mundane task.
We're expecting great
things from you, Amelia.
Yes, Father.
You are the eldest daughter
of House Rose,
the leader of the three great houses.
Compete like your life depends on it.
I understand.
Especially concerning Algren.
Losing to Miss Ariane
is out of the question.
Never forget the position you're in.
Understood?
Yes, Father.
Ariane Algren?
Yes.
Ariane has already been selected
as one of Diom's representatives.
That makes sense, too.
Is she strong, this Ariane Algren?
She is.
Despite also coming from a great family,
she and Amelia are a little different.
How can I put it?
To me she seems like the type who takes pride
in being a noble, and can
turn that into strength.
Being a noble...
I saw her practice once.
Even though she's younger than me,
her movements were truly marvelous.
Like a majestic bird soaring across the sky!
She's a formidable opponent,
but I know Amelia will
give her a good fight.
Yes. That's what I believe.
In any case, Miss Rebecca is going
to take first place by a huge margin,
just like last year!
Oh, Dina.
The winner is Amelia Rose.
Having won all her matches, she has secured
a spot for the Magic Chevalier!
Wow, she's in first place!
Amelia did it!
Most of her fights were
done in under ten seconds.
But it looks like her opponent, Alium,
made it through the qualifiers
in second place.
I've never seen him like that.
Is that right?
Great work, Miss Amelia!
Just as expected!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
We'll be cheering for you
in the main matches, too!
We all will!
I need to meet everyone's expectations.
My father's expectations.
Here, take this.
I'm sure it'll be useful some day.
Ray?
What are you doing here?
Congratulations on making
it through the qualifiers.
Thank yo—
It was too easy,
and it makes you uneasy.
"Am I good enough like this?"
That's what you're thinking.
Do you want to become strong?
Ariane is going to be in the rookie
bracket of the Magic Chevalier.
She's stronger than me...
We have less than a month left until
the tournament, but I could train you.
Really? But you're—
It's fine.
Since I'll only be instructing,
I won't need to release my abilities.
My master also lent me this.
What is that?
The Ainsworth-style boot camp.
This is what I used to
build my own foundation.
I completed it when I was little.
I'll do it!
That's the spirit!
Then, follow me, Amelia!
The path ahead is going to be brutal.
But if you make it to the
end, you can get stronger.
So much stronger than you are now.
Okay?
The first time I met Ariane was at one
of the parties for the upper nobility.
Are you Amelia?
I'm Ariane Algren.
Want to come play with me?
Being the same age, we naturally
became friends after that.
Let's go, Amelia!
W-Wait for me!
Amelia, this is a stag beetle.
Its horn is so big!
I won.
We had so much fun.
I loved her with all my heart.
Is something the matter?
Thank you for always playing with me.
I'm also always grateful for you.
Really?
Yes.
I do worry that you actually resent me for
always dragging you all over the place...
I'd never resent you!
If it wasn't for you,
I think I'd just be inside all the time.
But you're the one who got
me outside, so thank you!
Amelia.
We will always be friends.
Yes.
Always, always.
Always, always, always.
We were so close, but...
That was the last time we were really friends.
No, Ariane has always stayed the same.
It was me who changed.
Being a noble.
Being perceived as a noble.
At some point I realized that it
had become everything to me.
In order to survive.
I need to win.
It looks like Ray's not here yet.
Good morning, Amelia.
Ray. That is you, right?
I am Master White.
From here on, I am your instructor.
You are a private in training.
You answer with "ranger".
Got it?!
Uh? Huh?
I said you answer with "ranger",
Private Amelia!
First, I want you to lap the school,
enter the Kafka Forest
and then come back here.
That's easily twenty kilometers,
but you are not allowed to
use any body enhancements!
Twenty kilometers without body enhancements?
What is the response?
R-Ranger!
Many sorcerers try to rely
on body enhancement sorcery.
However, in the end, you only have
your own body to fall back on!
No matter how strong your will might be,
it's meaningless if your body cannot keep up!
Today's routine was light, but we'll
be going in earnest tomorrow.
This was "light"?
I said you answer with "ranger"!
Ranger!
Good!
What's up with her?
I guess she's doing Ray's special training.
It seems she's being pushed quite
hard from morning until evening.
So that's why Ray was going out in
the morning with that weird mask on.
A mask?
I was wondering why he
needs that to go running.
But now I get it.
You do?
I'm in Hell.
Ariane!
Wait, don't go!
Amelia.
E-Elisa?
You seem so alone.
Wai— Elisa!
There, there.
I-I'm stuck.
Poor Amelia.
Claris?!
Huh? Why?!
Is this... H-Heaven?
Bunny bun.
Amelia!
R-Ray, y-you're too close!
Want a bite?
Private Amelia! Time to report for duty!
You have one minute to get ready.
This can't be happening.
Are you still sleeping?!
I told you, you answer with "ranger"!
Hurry up!
I'll be waiting for you downstairs.
Ray!
Huh?
What are you doing out here so early
in the morning with that mask?!
What am I doing?
You mean the Ainsworth-style wake-up call?
Also, I am not Ray.
I am Master White!
Honestly, Ray...
I don't care about the official name for it!
Just stop coming into the girls' dormitory!
I see.
My apologies for not being more
considerate of the surroundings.
But I must say that you both look
very exquisite in your pajamas.
I don't care what you
think about that, either!
Oh, my.
Where do you think you're
going, Private Amelia?!
Oh, no!
Is that...
Miss Amelia?
I see.
We've got a runner this morning, huh?
However, I am a pro chaser!
Hey, Ray!
Let's go!
No!
You won't get away!
I was training on my own!
See you later.
I wasn't done with you!
I can't believe she ran away again.
Albert?
Oh, Ray, it's you.
Are you here all by yourself?
Where's your usual group?
Once in a while, I do like to be alone.
I see.
Hey.
How can I become strong?
To be honest, I still
have doubt in my heart.
I train every day,
but trying to shake off this doubt
is proving quite difficult.
There's no need to rush.
You've gotten stronger without
even knowing it.
And I'm sure you'll get even stronger.
So don't worry.
You really think so?
I do.
I guarantee it.
Hearing it from you makes me
believe it will actually happen.
I can't take this anymore!
This assignment is way too hard!
Your hair is all messed up.
Let me fix it for you.
I'm so sorry, Elisa.
I'd prefer a thank you over an apology.
Thank you.
Have you seen Amelia?
Amelia?
We haven't seen her.
I see.
Well, you can't run from me, Private Amelia!
I found you, Private Amelia!
Hey, you can't run in here!
This is too hard.
H-How did you find me here?
I used my abilities a bit.
You went that far?
Finding a private on the run is also
the instructor's responsibility.
I wasn't trying to run away, you know?
I just wanted to be alone for a little bit.
Worthless excuses!
For running away twice today,
a penalty will be added!
I'll also be explaining your self
training plan, which starts tomorrow!
My hand!
This hand?
I will not be releasing it until
we reach the training area.
You can count on that!
Let's go, Private Amelia!
I don't want to!
The only answer is "ranger"!
R-Ranger!
It's not easy...
...for her, either.
You want to form an Amelia cheering squad?
Yes!
I humbly ask for your approval!
But why should we do this?
Fighting when you feel the presence of those
cheering you on...
is a big help in itself.
However, I also believe that the
loudness of their cheers is also important.
I believe that we, with the most
impressive bulk at this academy,
could definitely become the
very best cheering squad!
Hm, now I see.
An Amelia cheering squad...
What could be better than that?
Let's lend our superior bulk
and cheer on Amelia, everyone!
Hell yeah!
Ray.
Yes!
Here's what you asked for.
Thank you.
I will not ask how you plan on using that.
You stay on your path of conviction!
Yes, sir!
Who was that?
Well, whatever.
That was amazing, Amelia!
You beat your previous time.
Thank you for coming out with
me so early in the morning.
It's the least we can do.
Claris and I were talking.
We were wondering if there was
anything we could do to help.
Thank you both.
Good job, Private Amelia.
Ranger!
I'm training as hard as I can!
Huh?
Who...
...was that?
No idea.
Become beautiful, become beautiful.
You have to say it, too, Dina.
I do?
Good work so early in the morning, Senpais!
Isn't that Diom's uniform?
But didn't she just call us senpai?
Oh, my.
It's perfect.
I'm currently absolutely without flaw.
But the real trial is yet to come.
Off to Diom Academy!
That's a cardboard box for you.
Nobody has noticed me.
Big sister, where are you?
Huh?
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
~ Next Episode Preview ~
Umm... This is the preview of the next episode of
The Iceblade Sorcerer Shall Rule the World!
Infiltrating Diom! The target is a
smart and beautiful young lady.
A very volatile teatime is about to begin!
"The Girl Who Became the World's Strongest
Sorcerer Infiltrates a Sorcery Academy".
Episode 7
The Girl Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Infiltrates a Sorcery Academy
This was Claris Cleveland!